http://www.alphaomegaswiss.com/privacy-security

(714) 692-8009 AboutEquipmentQualityContactRequest a Quote×Swiss MachiningSwiss Screw MachiningMicromachiningMedical MachiningDental MachiningScrew Machine ProductsPrecision CNC MachiningMachiningCNC MachiningCNC MillingCNC TurningCustom MachiningIndustriesMachining for IndustriesMedical MachiningDental MachiningMilitary MachiningElectronics MachiningMachined PartsCustom MachiningBushingsDowel PinsStandoffsShaftsInsertsMaterialsMaterial TypesStainless Steel MachiningTitanium MachiningBrass & Copper MachiningAluminum MachiningPlastic MachiningRequest A QuoteRequest A QuotePrivacy & SecurityIntegrity and Commitment, Guaranteed.Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the alphaomegaswiss.com and Alpha Omega Swiss and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Alpha Omega Swiss include alphaomegaswiss.com and Alpha Omega Swiss. The Alpha Omega Swiss website is a industrial machining site. By using the Alpha Omega Swiss website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationAlpha Omega Swiss may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Alpha Omega Swiss's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Alpha Omega Swiss may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Alpha Omega Swiss. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Alpha Omega Swiss website.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Alpha Omega Swiss's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.Alpha Omega Swiss encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Alpha Omega Swiss so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Alpha Omega Swiss is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Alpha Omega Swiss website.Use of your Personal InformationAlpha Omega Swiss collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.Alpha Omega Swiss may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Alpha Omega Swiss and its affiliates. Alpha Omega Swiss may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Alpha Omega Swiss does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.Alpha Omega Swiss may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Alpha Omega Swiss, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Alpha Omega Swiss will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Alpha Omega Swiss or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Alpha Omega Swiss; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Alpha Omega Swiss, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Alpha Omega Swiss website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Alpha Omega Swiss pages, or register with Alpha Omega Swiss site or services, a cookie helps Alpha Omega Swiss to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Alpha Omega Swiss website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Alpha Omega Swiss features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Alpha Omega Swiss services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal InformationTo secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Alpha Omega Swissuses the following: Let's Encrypt Authority X3 SSL Certificate When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Children Under ThirteenAlpha Omega Swiss does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.Opt-Out & UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Alpha Omega Swiss by contacting us here:- Web page: www.alphaomegaswiss.com- Email: info@alphaomegaswiss.com- Phone: (714) 692-8009Changes to this StatementAlpha Omega Swiss will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Alpha Omega Swiss encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Alpha Omega Swiss is protecting your information.Contact InformationAlpha Omega Swiss welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Alpha Omega Swiss has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Alpha Omega Swiss at:Alpha Omega Swiss, Inc.23305 La Palma Ave.Yorba Linda, CA 92887-4773, USAEmail Address:info@alphaomegaswiss.comTelephone number:(714) 692-8009Effective as of May 23, 2017Alpha Omega Swiss, inc.23305 La Palma Ave.Yorba Linda, CA 92887info@alphaomegaswiss.com(714) 692-8009 Customer Service(714) 604-2230 Quote Requests(714) 692-1461 FaxOur ServicesSwiss MachiningCNC MillingIndustries ServedMachined PartsMaterial TypesInfoAboutEquipmentQualityContactRequest A Quote©2017 Alpha Omega Swiss, Inc. Privacy & Security | SitemapWebsite by EMA
